<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kelly Integrations</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 13:32:29 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 13:32:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Construction Management Services</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Once the design is complete, KI will manage your construction project from start to finish. Keeping costs down, quality up and the schedule on track.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have experienced staff that will provide– quality control/assurance, pay application review, monitoring of field issues/resolutions, change order management and schedule oversight.  KI will supply an experienced Project Lead that will attend weekly site meetings, review the schedule, and perform field progress updates to ensure that the project is on-track; keeping our clients up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will facilitate the review and delivery of equipment for each particular site, take inventory and coordinate logistics if desired.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000/services/2016/12/29/service-two-content.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://127.0.0.1:4000/services/2016/12/29/service-two-content.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>services</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Integrations, Testing and Commissioning</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;KI will perform the necessary testing to ensure your system has been built properly, is performing at it’s maximum potential and conforms to the latest applicable standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone can start a project, but a successful system start-up and completion is accomplished with KI. Some companies assume that system start-up is the finish, walking away at this point, leaving the end users to work through issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KI believes in putting a bow around each project.  This is accomplished by ensuring a proper handoff with the end user’s maintenance staff resulting in a seamless transition of the new system. We can assist in choosing a new Computer Maintenance Management System or help integrate into an already existing one if desired.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000/services/2016/12/29/service-three-content.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://127.0.0.1:4000/services/2016/12/29/service-three-content.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>services</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On-Site Design Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;During the Design stage of your project, KI will provide a thorough on-site review of your project that will help to mitigate change orders and translate into time savings during the construction phase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will provide follow-up reviews on plan corrections to ensure the design team has provided cost effective solutions to the identified problems.Often times contract drawings are developed from previously flawed as-built drawings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KI will provide experienced personnel to inspect the site, including the mechanical, electrical and IT infrastructure to identify any major issues prior to moving forward. It’s critical that all major issues are identified during this stage to allow the project to stay on budget and schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000/services/2016/12/29/service-one-content.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://127.0.0.1:4000/services/2016/12/29/service-one-content.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>services</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>about</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Kelly Integrations (KI) is a Woman-Owned Business that provides Construction Management Services from Concept and Design Review through Construction Completion and Closeout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company was founded to provide specialized project oversight for large complex Baggage Handling Systems, Buildings and Public Works projects. We have experienced staff to manage the design, installation, testing and commissioning of your project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KI will provide: project management, coordination, quality assurance/quality control, progress updates, pay application review, change order management, and commissioning – ensuring that systems are built properly and test-ready. We will meet your every construction need as a Government Agency, Stakeholder, Contractor or Design Professional.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000/about/2016/12/29/about-section-content.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://127.0.0.1:4000/about/2016/12/29/about-section-content.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>about</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
